Cold, cold, pulping, my cannibal copy begins.
Like a factory machine, I lurk, dissonance
syndrome hunts underneath.
He said it was forever, the one and only night.
a part of him for me a debt he'll pay forever for
all eternity
a beat drops a fountain
This is my son, extension of me. My perfect boy,
my property. You will never be alone. You will
never be free. You are my comfort. extension of
me.
The world is loud and dirty. It's full of pain and
lies. I'll keep you safe forever. Just look in
mother's eyes. I'll be your hands and voice.
I'll be the air you breathe. You'll never have to
make a choice. You'll never have to leave.
This is my son. An extension of me. My perfect
boy. My property. You will never be alone. You
will never be free. You are my comfort.
An extension of me.
I'll keep you here. I'll keep you pure.
My only love.
My only cure.
You are mine.
You are mine. This is my song.
An extension of me My perfect boy My property You
will love
You will never be free You are my comfort An
extension of me
Dismount. Whisper.